Navigating the mumu-magisk-1click GitHub repository.
Clicking into the 'Tools' directory.
Hovering over the HMAL zip file link.
Clicking the download icon and downloading the HMAL zip file.
Navigating back and hovering over the LSPosed zip file link.
Clicking the download icon and downloading the LSPosed zip file.
Navigating back and hovering over the MT Manager MOD apk file link.
Clicking download, confirming duplicate, and downloading the MT Manager MOD apk file.
Closing the download dialog and hovering over the NeoZygisk zip file link.
Clicking the download icon and downloading the NeoZygisk zip file.
Minimizing the browser to show the MuMu Player 12 emulator window.
Showing the default MuMu Player home screen icons.
Opening Windows File Explorer and navigating to the Downloads folder.
Selecting and copying the four downloaded files (NeoZygisk, MT Manager, LSPosed, HMAL).
Closing the File Explorer window.
Clicking the MuMu file transfer/shared folder icon in the emulator sidebar.
Opening the MuMu12Shared folder on the host computer via the emulator dialog.
Dragging the four copied files from the host Downloads folder to the MuMu12Shared folder.
Closing the File Explorer and emulator file transfer dialog windows.
Opening the Kitsune Mask app in the emulator.
Kitsune Mask app opens, showing version and root status. Hiding the unofficial version warning.
Accessing Kitsune Mask settings and enabling the MagiskHide option.
Navigating to the Modules section in Kitsune Mask.
Selecting 'Install from storage' and installing the LSPosed module zip file.
Installing the NeoZygisk module zip file from storage.
Attempting to install the HMAL module zip file, which results in an 'Unzip error'.
Returning to the Modules screen, showing the two successfully installed modules.
Closing Kitsune Mask. Opening the host File Explorer (Downloads folder).
Opening the MT Manager app in the emulator.
Agreeing to MT Manager's User Agreement and granting Superuser (root) access.
Following prompts to grant MT Manager 'All files access' permission via Android settings.
Navigating within MT Manager to the /storage/emulated/0/SMuMu12Shared/Download/ folder.
Selecting the HMAL zip file and choosing 'Extract to current directory'.
Clicking the extracted HMAL apk file and initiating installation. Launching the app after successful installation.
The HMAL app opens, initially showing 'Module Not Activated'.
Navigating to HMAL settings and changing the theme to 'Always on' dark mode.
Scrolling down, enabling 'Void app data isolation' and granting HMAL Superuser rights.
Enabling 'Enforce data isolation for all apps' and 'Hide module icon in launcher'.
Navigating back to the HMAL home screen and confirming an exit prompt (in Chinese).
Closing HMAL and opening the MuMu Multi-instance Manager on the host desktop.
Closing the MuMu Multi-instance Manager.
Switching back to the web browser and searching Google for 'core patch'.
Clicking the GitHub link for LSPosed/CorePatch.
Navigating to the 'Releases' section of the CorePatch repository.
Clicking to download the `core-patch-4.6.apk` file from the latest release.
Confirming the download and opening the host computer's Downloads folder.
Dragging the downloaded Core Patch apk into the MuMu Multi-instance Manager to install on the running emulator.
The MuMu emulator instance restarts and loads various splash screens.
Emulator home screen appears. Closing the host Downloads folder overlay.
Opening the HMAL app (disguised as 'Android System'), showing an 'Xposed module not activated' notification.
Opening the Kitsune Mask app.
Checking the Modules tab, confirming NeoZygisk and LSPosed are active.
Browsing other Kitsune Mask tabs (Logs, Home, Settings).
Clicking the 'LSPosed loaded' notification to open the LSPosed manager app. Viewing the Modules list.
Enabling the Core Patch module within LSPosed and selecting 'System Framework' as its scope.
Navigating into Core Patch settings and enabling options: Disable compare signatures, Enhanced Mode, Bypass block, Bypass shared user verify, Disable Package Verification Agent.
Enabling the HMAL module within LSPosed and selecting 'System Framework' as its scope. Confirming an exit prompt (in Chinese).
Closing LSPosed and opening the MuMu Multi-instance Manager.
Stopping and then restarting the 'DEMO-1' MuMu emulator instance.
Emulator has loaded. Opening the Kitsune Mask app.
Navigating to Kitsune Mask Settings -> Configure MagiskHide and adding 'DarkClan' and 'Core Patch' to the hide list.
Closing Kitsune Mask.
Opening the HMAL app, which now correctly shows 'Module Activated'.
Navigating to HMAL -> App manage. Enabling 'Enable hide' for DarkClan, Core Patch, HMAL, Kitsune Mask, and MT Manager.
Returning to the HMAL home screen and closing the app.
Opening the Google Play Store, which now loads without requiring sign-in immediately (though sign-in is still needed for downloads).
Switching to a web browser tab displaying a Platinmods forum thread for a Dark Clan game mod.
Switching back to the Google Play Store and searching for 'Dark Clan: Squad Idle RPG'.
Clicking the 'Install' button for the Dark Clan game on the Play Store.
Switching back to the Platinmods browser tab, scrolling to download links, clicking the PM Patcher download link, confirming duplicate, downloading, and opening the host Downloads folder containing the patcher apk.
Downloading the PM Patcher apk file from Platinmods via the browser.
Dragging the downloaded PM Patcher apk from the host Downloads folder into the MuMu Multi-instance Manager to install it on the emulator.
Briefly showing the host Downloads folder again.
The Dark Clan game finishes installing in the emulator's Google Play Store.
Opening the newly installed PM Patcher app in the emulator.
Opening the Dark Clan game app in the emulator.
Dark Clan game shows a LIAPP Alert security check for rooting ("/bin/su"). Clicking OK.
The Dark Clan game closes unexpectedly after the security check.
Opening the HMAL app. Navigating to App manage -> DarkClan -> App settings.
Enabling the 'Enable hide' option specifically for the Dark Clan app within HMAL.
Navigating back to HMAL settings. Enabling 'Void app data isolation' and 'Enforce data isolation for all apps'.
Navigating to HMAL -> App manage -> DarkClan -> Clear data. Confirming the action.
Closing the HMAL app.
Opening the PM Patcher app.
Closing PM Patcher and opening the Dark Clan game app again.
Dark Clan game starts loading (Gameberry Studio logo).
A "Browser keeps stopping" error appears. Closing the error dialog.
Accepting the Dark Clan Game Terms and Conditions.
Accepting the Nighttime Push Consent prompt.
Initiating Google Sign-in within the Dark Clan game.
Dark Clan game continues loading (User data, Check server, Game loading).
Switching back to the PM Patcher app.
The PM Patcher app interface is shown (Mod By JokerART).
Selecting the target package for patching: `studio.gameberry.idledarkknight`.
Clicking 'Attach To PID Process'. A success message appears.
Clicking 'Create New Instance MemoryPatch'. A "Please wait" message appears.
Switching back to the Dark Clan game app.
The game finishes loading and enters the main game interface.
Showing Dark Clan gameplay: character stats, enhancing allies, combat.
Exiting the Dark Clan game.
Re-launching the Dark Clan game.
The game loads successfully again, indicating the patch and hiding methods worked.
Demonstrating more Dark Clan gameplay and navigating various in-game menus.
Closing the game and switching to the web browser, showing the mumu-magisk-1click GitHub README.
Scrolling through the "Visual Settings Guide" comparing Chinese and English UI elements.
Highlighting the command used to restore original MuMu settings.
Scrolling through the rest of the README, showing sections like Requirements, Disclaimer, and License, along with configuration screenshots.
Browsing the 'ChineseAssets' folder contents on GitHub, displaying Chinese UI screenshots.
Browsing the 'assets' folder contents on GitHub, displaying the corresponding English UI screenshots for various MuMu settings menus.
Returning to the README's Visual Settings Guide table.
Highlighting the relative path link to the Chinese UI assets folder within the table.
Returning to the MuMu emulator home screen, concluding the demonstration.